Noah Huffman

4234008546 | noahhuffman05@gmail.com | 1256 Coffelt Rd, Hixson, TN

Summary

After several years of experience in the customer service industry, and even more experience doing manual labor, I decided to start my own pressure washing business. I did this for about a year before returning to college, and was able to learn skills related to communication, money management, and self-discipline, among others.

However, I have always wanted to be a professional software developer, which is why I decided to go back to school and study Computer Science. I am now taking Java and Python classes at UTC, while learning C++ and refining my Python/Java skills on my own time. The most current language I have been studying is React.js, mostly through Pluralsight and YouTube. I am a critical thinking yet coachable, and friendly person, and I'm excited to learn new skills, and to sharpen those I already possess.

Experience

Unmanned Systems Lab | Chattanooga, Tennessee MatLab Programmer | 01/2021 - 06/2021

I worked at this lab for several months, which was owned by the Engineering Dean at the University I attend. I used MatLab with the intent of figuring out how to program a robot to detect when an Alzheimer's patient was in distress, and potentially in danger. I wish I could have stayed, but I was forced to leave for Covid-related reasons.

Volkswagen Group Chattanooga Operations | Chattanooga, Tennessee Production Team Member | 08/2022 - Present

I currently work the night shift on the Assembly Line at Volkswagen Chattanooga.

Randy Stansell Remodeling | Chattanooga, TN Carpenter | 05/2016 - 05/2019

I have worked off and on with this man since I was 12 years old. He taught me many helpful carpentry related skills, and taught be the importance of having a good work ethic.

Chick-fil-A I Hixson, TN

Cashier/Customer Service | 06/2019 - 02/2020

I learned to get along with fellow employees and provide excellent customer service to our customers.

PUBLIX SUPER MARKETS various locations | Hixson, TN

Shelf Stocker and Loader | 02/2020 - 09/2020

I was responsible for knowing the location of every product we sold, and for being able to communicate clearly with customers, despite any frustration they might have had.

Skills

ReactJS, Java, Python, C++, Spanish, HTML, CSS, Visual Studio, Eclipse, Entrepreneurship, Carpentry, Renovation, Customer Service, Communication skills

Education

University of Tennessee - Chattanooga | Chattanooga, TN Computer Science | 12/2024

Currently completing Java and Python courses in college, while simultaneously studying web-development through React.js, C++, HTML, and CSS on my own.